[{"answer": "We could be zipping all over the place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "They never try anything", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "They never try anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No harm!", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Dump her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " I once broke up with someone for not offering me pie", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What's me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Get out", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What's going on here? How do you think this happened", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You think that could be a coincidence my friend? Is that possible?", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So you think you can put the suit aside and hold it for me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh yes, of course, and we have to be fair.   ", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It will be a funky adventure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, how about you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Don't fill up on the bread. I'm making you a very special dinner. Very special.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Ah, my friend! Tonight you in for a real treat. I'm personnaly going to prepare the dinner for you and my Audrey. ", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You bastard! You hid the suit", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I hope you rot in that suit. I'm gonna get you for this. I don't know how, but I'm gonna get you. You are going to pay", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend get the car.", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "So how was the pie", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I lost it two days ago. I've been faking it so I wouldn't hurt her feelings", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pie.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'll let her down easy. All right.  Well, hi Olive.  No, no. No more of that. There's something I have to tell you", "qsentId": 24}]